
<?xml-model href="RelaxNG3.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<root>
    <metadata>
        <title>EXCLUSIVE! 6 QUESTIONS WITH JUNG KOOK, CALVIN KLEIN’S NEWEST GLOBAL
            AMBASSADOR</title>
        <writer>FARISIA THANG</writer>
        <datePublished date="2023-03-29">MARCH 29, 2023</datePublished>
    </metadata>
    <introduction>
        <p num="1">
            <band full="Bangtan Sonyeondan">BTS’</band> Jung Kook is officially the face of Calvin
            Klein! The <nationality>South Korean</nationality> singer-songwriter, record producer,
            and dancer joins <a
                href="https://elle.com.sg/2023/01/16/look-good-and-feel-good-with-calvin-kleins-latest-collection-for-the-lunar-new-year/"
                >Calvin Klein</a> as the newest global ambassador. But let’s be real… Fans made
            their theories and saw it coming shortly after the global head of creative <person
                role="Head of Creative">Cédric Murac</person> followed him on Instagram
                <parenthesis>(back when he had Instagram)</parenthesis>. We knew it was going to
            happen, we were just waiting for the official announcement <parenthesis>(and pictures,
                let’s be honest)</parenthesis>. </p>
        <p num="2"> He makes his debut for the brand in a new campaign
            wearing the brand’s Spring 2023 collections. Shot by <person role="photographer">Park
                Jong Ha</person>, the campaign captures him in new styles, including the <clothingItems>
                <item>90s Straight denim and Body Jeans</item>
                <item>Relaxed Fit Denim Shirt</item>
                <item>Oversized Denim Jacket</item>
                <item>Relaxed Fit Standard Logo Crewneck Tee</item>
            </clothingItems>. </p>
        <p num="3"> On this announcement, Jung Kook shares <statement>“I have been a fan of Calvin Klein for
                a long time, and I’m thrilled to be their newest global ambassador. This partnership
                is very special, as Calvin Klein’s heritage and brand values resonate with me. My
                music is how I communicate with my fans around the world, and I see this partnership
                as an opportunity to connect with them in a new way. I’m incredibly excited for
                people to see a new side of me in this first campaign for the brand.”</statement>
        </p>
        <p num="4"> In an exclusive interview with <magazine>ELLE Singapore</magazine>, Jung Kook talks
            about his latest creative inspirations, where he feels most comfortable, and what
            boldness means to him. </p>
    </introduction>
    <interview>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-1.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="1">When did you first hear of Calvin Klein? What was your first impression of the
            brand and how has that changed since?</question>
        <answer num="1">I don’t exactly remember when was the first time I heard of
            Calvin Klein, but it was after I moved to <city country="South Korea">Seoul</city>. At
            that time, I wasn’t familiar with many designer brands, but I knew Calvin Klein mostly
            for their signature underwear. Since then, it’s always been my favourite brand that I
            wear all the time.</answer>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-2.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="2">How would you describe Calvin Klein? What Calvin Klein items do you wear on a
            daily basis?</question>
        <answer num="2">I would say Calvin Klein is <quotations>“one of my closest
                friends.”</quotations> I do wear Calvin Klein underwear on a daily basis, and I
            can’t even pick one particular item as I just have so many. Actually, it was my first
            time wearing essential items from Calvin Klein Jeans when I was shooting the brand’s
            Spring 2023 campaign, and I loved them. It’s a new look for me, but I feel comfortable
            and confident that I think I would wear them a lot.</answer>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-3.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="3">What has inspired you creatively recently?</question>
        <answer num="3">I don’t think I have any specific inspirations lately, but
            usually, I get inspired by people who are good at what they do—like artists who make
            killing music, for instance—or people whom I respect.</answer>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-4.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-5.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="4">What’s a place where you feel most comfortable being yourself?</question>
        <answer num="4">Home is where I feel most comfortable and being myself. Like
            the feeling you get when you are wearing Calvin Klein underwear!
                <parenthesis>(laughs)</parenthesis></answer>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-6.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="5">What does boldness mean to you? What makes you feel bold?</question>
        <answer num="5">To me, boldness is like energy that comes from a powerful
            desire for something. I’m normally not a bold type, but when I get drawn into something
            I want or like, I suddenly become a different person.</answer>
        <image
            src="https://elle.com.sg/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Exclusive-ELLE-Singapore-interview-Jung-Kook-Calvin-Kleins-Newest-Global-Ambassador-7.jpg"/>
        <credit>Photo: Courtesy of <person role="photographer">Park Jong Ha</person> for Calvin
            Klein</credit>
        <question num="6">What does it mean for you to join Calvin Klein as a global ambassador?</question>
        <answer num="6">I’m very happy to be the face of Calvin Klein Jeans and
            Calvin Klein Underwear. Calvin Klein has always been my favourite brand. Regardless of
            ambassadorship, I would wear the brand for its unquestionable quality and timeless
            designs. My Calvins elevate my everyday.</answer>
    </interview>
</root>
